Leonard Arakasamy

Ampang, Selangor, Malaysia



linkedin.com/in/leonard-arakasamy-553835b5



leondesigner@outlook.my

Summary

I was working for 3 years as Technical Support Engineer Level 1 and HLC Lotus Notes Domino System Administrator Level 1. My achievement were was working as Technical Support Engineer where i could finished and handle technical issues task and im the highest percentage where can handle a lot of technical issues regarding hardware issues. Currently,im working on Fiverr and i wanna create an application.

Experience



Web Developer

Fiverr

Dec 2019 - Present (8 months +)

Create web for customers....

| Lotus Notes Administrator

Teknod Sdn. Bhd.

Jun 2013 - Dec 2013 (7 months)

Handle Lotus Note Administrrator

| Technical Support

Encoral Digital Solutions Sdn. Bhd.

Oct 2010 - May 2012 (1 year 8 months)

Assembly, repair, service, maintain, troubleshoot and service PC and laptop.

Education

☐ Codecademy (Self taught Coder)

Web Designer and Web Deve

2013 - 2020

HTML,CSS,Javascript... Web Designer and Developer.

Industrial Training Institute Nibong Tebal, Penang

Certificate in Computer Networking

2008 - 2009

Skills

Teamwork • Microsoft Office • Strategy • Strategic Planning • Communication Skill • HTML,CSS,Javascript